(Penny:)But what if you need it?
My expenses account for 46.9 percent
of my after-tax income.
(Sheldon:)The rest is divvied up
between a small savings account...
(Sheldon:)...this deceptive container
of peanut brittle...
(Sheldon:)...and the hollowed-out buttocks
of a superhero action figure...
(Sheldon:)...who shall remain nameless
for his own protection.
(Sheldon:)Or her own protection.
(Sheldon:)- Take some.
- Really? I mean, are you sure?
(Sheldon:)I see no large upcoming expenditures.
Unless they develop technology
to fuse my skeleton...
(Sheldon:)...with Adamantium like Wolverine.
(Penny:)Are they working on that?
(Sheldon:)I sincerely hope so.
(Penny:)Okay. Well, thank you.
(Leonard:)Hmm.